# ORLANDOREYNOSO

# IT SUPPORT SPECIALIST | SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR

# **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

Windows Server Administrator

Virtualization
SQL Server
Web Server
Print Server
Windows, Mac, and Linux OS
Firewall and Security
Office 365
Programming (VB.NET and C#)
Web Development (HTML, CSS, JS, WP, GIT, Bootstrap)
Enterprise-Class Antivirus Solutions
Networking
iOS and Android OS
Help Desk

## **PERSONAL SKILLS**

Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated
Capability of Analysis
Problem Solving

## LANGUAGES

English: Fluent Spanish: Native French: Beginner

### CONTACT

(829) 307-8247 Ced: 001-1663081-5 OrlandoReynoso1983@gmail.com www.OrlandoReynoso.net LinkedIn

#### REFERENCES

Available upon request

HIGHLIGHTS: Successful IT support and system administrator with more than 16 years of experience in the field. always stimulating myself and coworkers to work hard looking to achieve beyond the expected results refreshing knowledge and creativity. My collaborative leadership, persuasive skills, my positive attitude, and my solid work ethic have allowed me to obtain solid knowledge in many technologies and teamwork. I can prioritize, work under pressure, and meet deadlines. I am always highly motivated to learn new things from everyone around me. Seeking to use my expertise, skills, and abilities to contribute to your organization's success.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **APLICATION SUPPORT ANALYST**

VISIUMKMS | 2020 - PRESENT

Troubleshooting issues in the product (application and data), database server, web server (IIS), and networks, to minimize risk of disruptions. Creating Microsoft SQL Server and Oracle Databases scripts to identify and correct data integrity issues in customer's data. Managing ticket workload across a number of customers, escalating issues where appropriate and providing resolution to issues. Supporting updates to products and services in both test and live system environments, in compliance with defined procedures, And much more.

## IT SUPPORT MANAGER AND SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR

MEPyD | 2013 - 2020

Worked as Windows System Administrator 2012/2016 servers, AD, GPO, DNS, DHCP, NAS storage, System Backup and restore management, Print and Hyper-V Server, Windows 7, 8.1 and 10, Installed and configured PCs, DVRs, Access Controls, Printers, networking hardware and software, operating systems, applications, shared folders, Microsoft Office 2007, 2013, 2016 and 365. Monitored, optimized, and configured networks with security appliance / firewall (FortiGate UTM, Antivirus, Web Filter, Application Control, Email Filter, Instruction Protection, Traffic Shaper). Collaborated on developing systems Client - Server using VB.Net and SQL Server.

#### IT SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR

CENTRO MEDICO SANTIAGO APOSTOL | ARS-CMD | COMPUNET 2004 - 2013

Managed computers, networks, information systems, databases, and ensured related issues to information technology worked effectively. Worked as Windows System Administrator 2003/2008/2012 servers, AD, GPO, DNS, IIS, DHCP server, ISA server, Windows XP and 7. Access Controls, Printers, and applications. Networking (cabling, switches, routers, and patch panels).

### **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR IN BUSINESS INFORMATICS | SUMMA CUM LAUDE UNIVERSIDAD ABIERTA PARA ADULTOS (UAPA), Santiago, D.R. 2011 - 2015